<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<odoo noupdate="0">

    <record id="data_pegi_age_3" model="pegi.age">
        <field name="name">PEGI 3</field>
        <field name="logo" type="base64" file="pegi/static/img/age/PEGI_3.png"/>
        <field name="description">The content of games with a PEGI 3 rating is considered suitable for all age groups.
            The game should not contain any sounds or pictures that are likely to frighten young children. A very mild
            form of violence (in a comical context or a childlike setting) is acceptable. No bad language should be
            heard.
        </field>
    </record>

    <record id="data_pegi_age_7" model="pegi.age">
        <field name="name">PEGI 7</field>
        <field name="logo" type="base64" file="pegi/static/img/age/PEGI_7.png"/>
        <field name="description">Game content with scenes or sounds that can possibly be frightening to younger
            children should fall in this category. Very mild forms of violence (implied, non-detailed, or non-realistic
            violence) are acceptable for a game with a PEGI 7 rating.
        </field>
    </record>

    <record id="data_pegi_age_12" model="pegi.age">
        <field name="name">PEGI 12</field>
        <field name="logo" type="base64" file="pegi/static/img/age/PEGI_12.png"/>
        <field name="description">Video games that show violence of a slightly more graphic nature towards fantasy
            characters or non-realistic violence towards human-like characters would fall in this age category. Sexual
            innuendo or sexual posturing can be present, while any bad language in this category must be mild.
        </field>
    </record>

    <record id="data_pegi_age_16" model="pegi.age">
        <field name="name">PEGI 16</field>
        <field name="logo" type="base64" file="pegi/static/img/age/PEGI_16.png"/>
        <field name="description">This rating is applied once the depiction of violence (or sexual activity) reaches a
            stage that looks the same as would be expected in real life. The use of bad language in games with a PEGI 16
            rating can be more extreme, while the use of tobacco, alcohol or illegal drugs can also be present.
        </field>
    </record>

    <record id="data_pegi_age_18" model="pegi.age">
        <field name="name">PEGI 18</field>
        <field name="logo" type="base64" file="pegi/static/img/age/PEGI_18.png"/>
        <field name="description">The adult classification is applied when the level of violence reaches a stage where
            it becomes a depiction of gross violence, apparently motiveless killing, or violence towards defenceless
            characters. The glamorisation of the use of illegal drugs and of the simulation of gambling, and explicit
            sexual activity should also fall into this age category.
        </field>
    </record>

</odoo>
