<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<odoo noupdate="0">

    <record id="data_pegi_content_violence" model="pegi.content">
        <field name="name">VIOLENCE</field>
        <field name="logo" type="base64" file="pegi/static/img/content/VIOLENCE.png"/>
        <field name="description">The game contains depictions of violence. In games rated PEGI 7 this can only be
            non-realistic or non-detailed violence. Games rated PEGI 12 can include violence in a fantasy environment or
            non-realistic violence towards human-like characters, whereas games rated PEGI 16 or 18 have increasingly
            more realistic-looking violence.
        </field>
    </record>

    <record id="data_pegi_content_bad_language" model="pegi.content">
        <field name="name">BAD LANGUAGE</field>
        <field name="logo" type="base64" file="pegi/static/img/content/BAD_LANGUAGE.png"/>
        <field name="description">The game contains bad language. This descriptor can be found on games with a PEGI 12
            (mild swearing), PEGI 16 (e.g. sexual expletives or blasphemy) or PEGI 18 rating (e.g. sexual expletives or
            blasphemy).
        </field>
    </record>

    <record id="data_pegi_content_fear" model="pegi.content">
        <field name="name">FEAR</field>
        <field name="logo" type="base64" file="pegi/static/img/content/FEAR.png"/>
        <field name="description">This descriptor may appear as 'Fear' on games with a PEGI 7 if it contains pictures or
            sounds that may be frightening or scary to young children, or as 'Horror' on higher-rated games that contain
            moderate (PEGI 12) or intense and sustained (PEGI 16) horror sequences or disturbing images (not necessarily
            including violent content).
        </field>
    </record>

    <record id="data_pegi_content_gambling" model="pegi.content">
        <field name="name">GAMBLING</field>
        <field name="logo" type="base64" file="pegi/static/img/content/GAMBLING.png"/>
        <field name="description">The game contains elements that encourage or teach gambling. These simulations of
            gambling refer to games of chance that are normally carried out in casinos or gambling halls. Some older
            titles can be found with PEGI 12 or PEGI 16, but PEGI changed the criteria for this classification in 2020,
            which made that new games with this sort of content are always PEGI 18.
        </field>
    </record>

    <record id="data_pegi_content_sex" model="pegi.content">
        <field name="name">SEX</field>
        <field name="logo" type="base64" file="pegi/static/img/content/SEX.png"/>
        <field name="description">This content descriptor can accompany a PEGI 12 rating if the game includes sexual
            posturing or innuendo, a PEGI 16 rating if there is erotic nudity or sexual intercourse without visible
            genitals or a PEGI 18 rating if there is explicit sexual activity in the game. Depictions of nudity in a
            non-sexual context do not require a specific age rating, and this descriptor would not be necessary.
        </field>
    </record>

    <record id="data_pegi_content_drugs" model="pegi.content">
        <field name="name">DRUGS</field>
        <field name="logo" type="base64" file="pegi/static/img/content/DRUGS.png"/>
        <field name="description">The game refers to or depicts the use of illegal drugs, alcohol or tobacco. Games with
            this content descriptor are always PEGI 16 or PEGI 18.
        </field>
    </record>

    <record id="data_pegi_content_discrimination" model="pegi.content">
        <field name="name">DISCRIMINATION</field>
        <field name="logo" type="base64" file="pegi/static/img/content/DISCRIMINATION.png"/>
        <field name="description">The game contains depictions of ethnic, religious, nationalistic or other stereotypes
            likely to encourage hatred. This content is always restricted to a PEGI 18 rating (and likely to infringe
            national criminal laws).
        </field>
    </record>

    <record id="data_pegi_content_in_game_purchases" model="pegi.content">
        <field name="name">IN-GAME PURCHASES</field>
        <field name="logo" type="base64" file="pegi/static/img/content/IN_GAME_PURCHASES.png"/>
        <field name="description"><![CDATA[The game offers players the option to purchase digital goods or services with
            real-world currency. Such purchases include additional content (bonus levels, outfits, surprise items,
            music), but also upgrades (e.g. to disable ads), subscriptions to updates, virtual coins and other forms of
            in-game currency.
            <br/>
            This content descriptor is sometimes accompanied by an additional notice if the in-game purchases include
            random items (like loot boxes or card packs). Paid random items comprise all in-game offers where players
            don't know exactly what they are getting prior to the purchase. They can be purchased directly with real
            money and/or exchanged for an in-game virtual currency. Depending on the game, these items may be purely
            cosmetic or they may have functional value.
            <br/>
            The notice is always displayed underneath or near the age label and content descriptors.]]>
        </field>
    </record>

</odoo>
